Dainger James Adams

900 e 250 s, Salt lake City, Utah 84102 (801) 388-4185 adamsda96@gmail.com

Summary of Qualifications

Analytical thinking skills with research experience

Worked with The University of Utah on research projects.

Experience as a group leader

Had a leader position in University of Utah athletics department.

Dynamic in work

Able to problem solve and work around most things to come to desired result.

Education

University of Utah Salt Lake City, UT

Currently studying: Chemical Engineering Graduation: Spring 2018

Work Experience

University Pharmacy Salt Lake City, UT
Programmer February 2017-Present

Using python, javascript and SQL to create a database that stores formulas, chemical, other information.

University of Utah

Salt Lake City, UT

Intern August 2015-May 2015

Worked with Arduinos and Matlab to complete research on CO levels in Salt Lake City.

Professor: Tony Butterfield

Honors and Activities

Envirothon – Participation – 2012 & 2013

Science Fair – Alternatives for DEET insect repellent - 2nd Place in district –2013

Science Fair – Soda lime as an affective CO₂ absorber for cars - 3rd Place in district – 2014

Sterling scholar- Science - Bonneville High School - 2013-2014

Technical project – cooperated with other classmates to build a bioreactor to produce bio-diesel – 2015

Skills

Microsoft Word Matlab C++
Microsoft PowerPoint SQL Python

Microsoft Excel Android programing Research Experience